greenlivingtips.com 2017-03-25

# Privacy statement | Green Living Tips

GreenLivingTips.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy to our visitors and subscribers.

This statement is subject to change without notice and users of our service are expected to review this page on a regular basis.

IP Address

An IP (Internet Protocol) address is a unique identifier for a computer on a particular network; including the Internet. When you log on to the Internet, your computer is issued with an IP address.

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, for security purposes and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is used to gather broad demographic information.

Cookies and advertising

We use cookies to enable functionality of this site.

Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to this website.

Google’s use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to users based on their visit to this site and/or other sites on the Internet.

Users may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting the [ads preference manager](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/). (Alternatively, you can opt out of a third-party vendor’s use of cookies for interest based advertising by visiting [aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/).)  
Links to other sites

This site contains links to other sites. GreenLivingTips.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

Public Forums

This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information

Security

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Details of our subscribers are kept in secure areas of our server and with encrypted passwords. All activity on GreenLivingTips.com is logged for security purposes.

Legal Issues

We may disclose personal information in response to a relevant legal process, for example, in response to a court order or in response to a law enforcement agency’s formal request.

Childrens’ Usage

Taming the Beast.net strongly urges parents to monitor children’s usage of the Web, including this web site.

Mailing lists

Any visitor signing up for any of our in-house mailing lists are assured that we do not, under any circumstances sell, rent or otherwise redistribute our mailing lists to any other company. The only exception to this would be in the situation that GreenLivingTips.com or a particular service area of GreenLivingTips.com is sold to another party where mailing list subscriber information would constitute a part of that sale.

Abuse/Inappropriate Communications

We reserve the right to forward abusive and inappropriate communications to the service providers of the originating communication and to relevant local, state, federal and international authorities.

Choice/Opt-Out

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor.

You can use our  [Contact ](https://www.greenlivingtips.com/pages/Contact-Us.html) form to opt out of any further communications from us.

Contacting us

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, we recommend you review our terms of service or you can submit your questions via our [Contact ](https://www.greenlivingtips.com/pages/Contact-Us.html) form; or via the following address:

Michael Bloch  
Box 2135  
Hackham  
South Australia 5163
